Raj has joined us from the state.
Raj, first of all, heartiest greetings of the New Year.
Tell me what is your question, Sir,
I have 450 shares of ICI, which
I bought at 860, so I need
information,
experts should tell me about it, should I exit or
hold it for now, and I bought it for a short term,
but now I can hold it for a month or a
month and a half, sir,
and how much did you tell the shares to be 400, yes, that was a
typing mistake, it went down to 150,
but 450 is fine, okay, so
Sachin ji, I would like to come to you, just
look at the stock, if you look at its buying, it is
seen downwards at around 4,
recently the stock had given a pullback from the
November low, but back in December,
from December 16, we are seeing that perhaps selling started from there
and it is seen going down
breaking the pullback from where it came, the
stock is trading around the multi-month low, so tell me if there are any
signs of recovery from here.  Is there any
bearish
sentiment building up towards the downside? Look,
it has tested some good supports on the weekly charts,
1730 and 1740, that was a level.
After testing these levels, it
slid from here and the upside momentum continued here.
So, I
think these are the immediate supports. If the 1730 position is broken, then it can be held
with a stop loss below it.
But in case the 1730
levels are broken, then the
downside momentum can possibly continue till 1600 or 150.
I think for now,
hold the positions with a stop loss below 1730. If there is any further
rebound, there will be
possibilities of reaching around 1900 and 1950 on the upside.
But in case the 1730 levels are broken,
then there will be possibilities of testing the 1650 levels.  It would be
advisable to exit the position there.